// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!
module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Where did the Graboids hatch?', 
      a: 'Perfection, NV', 
      b: 'Rejection, NV',
      c: 'Obstruction, NV',
      d: 'Consumption, NV',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following can fly?', 
      a: 'a graboid', 
      b: 'a shrieker',
      c: 'an ass blaster',
      d: 'a butt bomber',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which country star blows up a graboid in her own basement?', 
      a: 'Trisha Yearwood', 
      b: 'Shania Twain',
      c: 'Taylor Swift',
      d: 'Reba McEntire',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What\'s the team on the hat that Burt Gummer wears throughout most of the movies?', 
      a: 'Atlanta Hawks', 
      b: 'Seattle Seahawks',
      c: 'St. Louis Cardinals',
      d: 'Baltimore Ravens',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which actor only appeared in the first Tremors but none of the sequels?', 
      a: 'Kevin Bacon', 
      b: 'Tom Hanks',
      c: 'Bill Murray',
      d: 'Bruce Willis',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many total Tremors films have been made?', 
      a: '3', 
      b: '4',
      c: '5',
      d: '6',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What\'s the name of the upcoming 7th Tremors Film?', 
      a: 'A Cold Day in Hell', 
      b: 'Island Fury',
      c: 'Killer Worms for Outerspace',
      d: 'Sharknado vs. Tremors',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What film did Kevin Bacon choose to star in instead of Tremors 2?', 
      a: 'Footloose', 
      b: 'Hollowman',
      c: 'Apollo 13',
      d: 'Sleepers',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where was Tremors 2 supposed to be filmed originally?', 
      a: 'Madagascar', 
      b: 'Australia',
      c: 'New Zealand',
      d: 'Thailand',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where was Perfection, NV actually located?', 
      a: 'Provo, UT', 
      b: 'Farmington NM',
      c: 'Lone Pine, CA',
      d: 'Amarillo, TX',
      answer: 'c'
    }
  ]
};